protogenist.com 2018-09-30

# Protogenist Info Systems Private Limited | Privacy Statement |Software Consulting | Enterprise Application Development | Integrated Business Solutions | Technology touches Excellence

One of the basic objectives of this website is to maintain your privacy because your privacy is important to Protogenist. This Privacy Statement demonstrates the information practices for Protogenist's and our affiliates' Web sites, including what type of information is gathered and tracked, how the information is used, and with whom the information is shared.

You may choose to give us personal information directly in a variety of situations like name and contact information to communicate with you, to process an order, to provide you with a subscription or a service, or to do business with us if you are a supplier or a business partner.

We may use information we collect about you to provide you with a personalized experience on our Web sites, such as providing you with content in which you may be interested and making navigation on our sites easier.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and/or to administer our Web site. This gives us an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous. We also provide "Live Chat" sessions on our Web sites to assist you while you're navigating through our sites; we will use personal information you provide via these sessions in accordance with this Privacy Statement.

This site contains links to other sites. Protogenist Info Systems Private Limited is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

##### Security

We take necessary steps to protect your personal information on our website. You should understand that the open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended. But Protogenist technical safeguards help us protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure.

If you have any queries or feedback regarding this Privacy Statement then you can contact Protogenist Info Systems Private Limited. Contact us

### Contact Us

Easy ways to get your Answer
